<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scene on Photonic Application Lab (PAL)</title>
    <link>https://dongbowei-lab.github.io/tags/scene/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scene on Photonic Application Lab (PAL)</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dongbowei-lab.github.io/tags/scene/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: Master Jacques Coppenole</title>
      <link>https://dongbowei-lab.github.io/chapter-iv-master-jacques-coppenole/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongbowei-lab.github.io/chapter-iv-master-jacques-coppenole/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low&lt;br&gt;&#xA;bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a&lt;br&gt;&#xA;large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter&lt;br&gt;&#xA;abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by&lt;br&gt;&#xA;the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the&lt;br&gt;&#xA;velvet and silk which surrounded him. Presuming that he was some groom who&lt;br&gt;&#xA;had stolen in, the usher stopped him.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computing at the speed of light</title>
      <link>https://dongbowei-lab.github.io/computing-at-the-speed-of-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongbowei-lab.github.io/computing-at-the-speed-of-light/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The human brain is often compared to a computer. Using electrical impulses, it receives inputs from the external world, integrates this information in a split second, and plans and executes responses. The brain’s immense information processing capabilities have also inspired the design of high power computing architectures and driven the development of artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For decades, devices like transistors and semiconductors that operate using the humble electron have dominated the computing world. However, as researchers begin to hit physical limits in how much processing power they can fit into an electronic chip, some are exploring new ways of building chips to overcome those limitations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
